

Akira Gil Lamagna Shopify Developer

#### **Personal Information**

Blk 2 Lot 17 Israel Street Phase 3B Palmera Springs Caloocan City, 1400

+639953557320 akiralamagna@gmail.com

## **Project Management**

Basecamp, Trello, Slack, JIRA, Hubspot, Zoho

## **Programming Language**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, Liquid, Ruby

## Professional skills

**Google Suite** 

Microsoft Office Tools

**Adobe Photoshop** 

**Adobe Lightroom** 

## Languages

**English** Proficient

**Tagalog** Native

## Profile

Seasoned and independent Shopify Developer with 2 years of experience in blending the art of design with skill of programming to deliver an immersive and engaging user experience through efficient website development, proactive feature optimization, and relentless debugging.

## Experience

### **Shopify Developer**

August 2019 - Present

- · Create, build and manage Shopify stores for clients, businesses and companies
- Deliver engaging user experience through optimization of images, cross-browser compatibility
- Expand features, refine code, and improve processes, producing smoother operations and enhancing user engagement
- Designed dynamic and browser compatible pages using Shopify page builder or other page building apps like Pagebuilder by Pagefly

# Technical Support Representative - Teleperformance, Fairview, Quezon City

Jun 2016 - Jul 2019

- Communicate with clients via phone calls to provide step-by-step solutions effective in resolving hardware or software problems
- Providing response and solutions to issues experienced by users of technological products or services
- Serve as the first point of contact for customers with complaints or questions concerning company technological products/services

#### **Education**

# Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering - STI College, Fairview, Quezon City

Jun 2015 - Mar 2016

• 3rd year undergraduate